Yeah.
I don't know how you got here.
That's a baby.
Well, hello.
How are you, Julie?
I'm muted. Sorry. How are you?
How are the babies?
Now you're not.
They're good. Thanks for asking.
Keeping us busy and perplexed and
OK.
overjoyed. All all these mixture emotions.
Completely.
Mhm.
Oh, I see. All right. Um,
let's let some people in here.
So it's nice, like,
if you're part of the team,
you just get to let yourself in.
But if you're outside the team,
I guess you need to be let in.
Hmm.
Right, 'cause you just came in.
You just entered. You just entered.
I guess I just clicked the link.
There you go. Let's get some others.
Hey, Chris.
How you doing? Happy Friday.
Oh, good. Happy Friday.
We're gonna, uh,
get everybody in and we'll do some intros,
but I appreciate you showing up early.
Yeah, thank you.
Thanks for thinking of us and thanks for
having Regeneron on.
Yeah, it's gonna be great.
I'm looking forward to this discussion.
Appreciate it.
Allison, nice to nice to have you join.
Hey, David, how are you?
It's good to see you.
Good, good. Yeah.
Nice to see your initials on our screen.
Yes.
You guys have. Please feel free to.
I don't know where you are,
what you're doing,
but always welcome to be on camera.
I'm just gonna let some folks in.
A day. Hello again.
How are you?
Yeah, I'm glad you're able to make it.
Yeah, me too.
So the Regeneron team, maybe 88 of you,
something like that, give or take.
Is that what you expect today,
Chris and Allison?
I'm not quite sure who expected.
I think in your the link you had sent out
there was a request for acceptance or or
deny, so I didn't see that on my end.
Mhm.
I think Sarah was gonna join for sure.
Alice and myself and then.
Got it.
Oh, there's Sarah now.
A few others were also invited,
It's there.
so I think you'll have a handful,
hopefully.
Good. Yeah, Matthew reached out.
He got something going on right now,
but he may join as the hour proceeds.
So, Sarah, hello. Happy Friday.
And um, Yep.
Hi. Hi.
I don't know why my camera's black. Oh,
here we go. Hi, how are you?
Good, good. Yeah.
Please join via camera if you can. So hey,
Am I on now?
Oh, there you are. Yes. Um, thank you.
It's very, uh.
that's a nice backdrop.
Biology look, molecular look,
I don't know. Yes,
Matthew has a a doctor's appointment.
I think that he'll try to join,
but Frank is joining us as well, I think.
And I did invite Priscilla and Jean
Francois, but I think they're on holidays.
Yeah, we'll just see who joins.
Yes, thank you for including us.
We appreciate it.
Oh, you're welcome. Oh,
it adds the conversation for sure. Oh,
there's Matthew. All right, coming in.
Yes.
Oh, there we go.
Um,
we were talking about like after college.
Mm-hmm. And I was asking.
Matthew, were your ears burning?
We were just talking about you.
I'm glad you could make it.
Yes, just getting settled in. Thank you.
We'll just let people in.
I'll probably go to three or four after
and then we'll get rolling with the
agenda.
Isaac, happy Friday.
And happy Friday to everyone.
Doctor Drews, always a pleasure.
Oh.
Thanks for having me.
OK.
Mhm. I think Lauren joined.
Where is Lauren? There you are, Lauren.
Thanks for joining.
Thanks so much for having me.
Yeah, you're welcome.
So what year are you, Lauren?
I just started my third year fellowship.
Nice.
Are you doing Cutaneous Clinic with Reed?
I am, yeah. I've been with Reed.
I've started in during residency and have
been able to continue that for the past
two years now.
Nice.
She's gonna be my successor, David.
Yeah.
Oh, those are some big shoes to fill.
I'll tell you.
That is for sure.
Are you kidding me? Come on.
Yeah,
it'll be interesting to see how it all
integrates in the years ahead.
OK.
I hope we're able to retain a multidisc
conference and everything, you know,
the way we do it.
Right.
Yeah. Are those conversations in the mix?
You guys talking about how that's gonna
get integrated with the farmer?
I actually haven't had a chance to speak
to David McDermott about that.
Gonna be interesting. Vishal,
thanks for joining us.
Hey guys, sorry, I'm other.
How are the kids? How are the kiddos?
Oh, you got him in the car. I love it.
You guys driving to Hershey now?
We're about an hour out from Hershey Park.
Mm.
Nice. That'll be an awesome weekend.
They're they're watching the Super.
They're watching the Super Mario.
Skype.
We're hearing a little bit of it too.
Very nice.
I know I'm gonna try to go on mute,
so 'cause it's right by my head.
It's right by my head.
Unless you want to hear Peaches, Peaches,
No problem, no.
Peaches by Jack Black.
So.
I don't know if we if we can make that
into, you know,
all the sea post inside jokes 323232.
Oh, you'll be.
You're creative enough to to make those.
I'm not sure I am, but uh, yeah,
I'm glad you you're glad able to make it.
Doctor Niam, nice to see you,
Doctor Kuselani.
Always a pleasure, David.
Yeah, it's always a pleasure.
Happy Friday, Dr. Knight.
Guiding.
Thanks for joining us.
Good to be here.
It's a good group.
We'll just give another minute or two
people are still coming in.
Oh.
Ross, looks like you are also in transit.
In transit, but not driving.
You got my almost full,
Good. Good. Hey, Molly.
almost undivided attention.
Doctor Sondak.
Greetings. Greetings.
Vernon.
Greetings to you.
Are things in Tampa these days nice and
sticky?
Oh, it's not too bad.
Oh.
The team.
Could be worse.
Doctor Kaufman, greetings.
Hello everyone.
Hello. Hello. All right,
why don't we roll?
I will start sharing my screen and then
we can get into it.
And there's one thing.
All right,
just give me a thumbs up and people can
Yeah, it looks good.
see the screen that I'm intending.
All right.
Well,
I'm just going to give one last render to
see if any last minute survey
participants can get included.
Thank you for those that filled it out.
All right,
so this is our little agenda for the hour.
It's packed, so we'll try to be efficient.
I thought we could do introduction
similar to we did last time.
If the SOCA members could just pop in
their affiliations and name and role in
the chat here, that would be great.
And.
And then the folks from Regeneron,
if you don't mind,
we'll just quickly go around and you can
introduce yourselves.
I'll just start here.
All right, all right. So Regeneron team,
I don't know, maybe Chris,
do you want to start and then just pass
it on to your colleagues? Just give,
you know, 10 seconds,
your name and what you do for Regeneron.
S.
Sure. Good afternoon, everyone.
Thanks for having me,
Regeneron on today's call. Dr. Miller,
thanks for reaching out and you know,
putting this together and including
Regeneron and CPOS data.
So my name is Chris Zajac.
I am a field medical scientist.
I cover Melanoma, non Melanoma.
Skin cancers and I work a lot in the
Boston area with Doctor Miller and his
colleagues,
and I'll pass it off over to Allison.
Hi, thanks. This is Alison Barry Amos.
I work with Chris on the field medical
OK.
team and I'm the regional director for
the East and I'm in the car,
so I can't see the next square.
So hopefully someone from.
Sarah, do you want to introduce yourself?
Yeah.
Sure. Thanks, Chris. Hi, good afternoon,
everyone. I'm Sara Niam,
Medical Director for Skin Cancer with
Medical Affairs at Regeneron.
And can take over.
It's a pleasure to be here.
And thank you for the invitation, David.
I'll pass it on to Matthew Fury.
Hi, I'm Matthew Fury,
Clinical Development at Regeneron.
I've been here about 10 years.
Medical oncologist by training,
but I'm learning Derm slowly and I work
with a great team here and thanks for
setting this up.
Yeah, you're welcome.
And I don't think it's so slowly, Matthew.
I think you're you're pretty up to speed
these days.
Anyone else from your team that I missed?
OK.
Yeah, we have a few more. Frank is on. Hi,
everyone. Thanks for having us today.
Frank.
Oh, Frank.
Frank Siebach-lo,
Program Head for the CMP of MAP program.
Good to see everyone.
Thanks again for having us.
Of course, Frank, thank you.
And then our Brian.
Yeah, Brian Burleson,
Field Medical West US Director. Thank you.
And then Kim.
Ryan, thank you.
Last Kim Primo,
I'm the trainer for medical affairs. Yeah,
And I think we.
Kim, thank you. Well,
thanks for being here.
thanks for having us.
This is obviously a very important paper,
very important study.
It's going to impact our field
significantly.
So I'm really looking forward to getting
everyone's impact and and learning more
about how they think it's going to
incorporate into their practice.
M.
So before we do that,
customary to our monthly meetings is
we're just going to do a quick journal
club in review,
look at what we've done over pastoralized
over the years and and see how that
information has affected our practice.
Just quick review on our most recent
perspective on the science piece,
then we'll do review of the data.
Data from the survey,
then we'll jump into the article and talk
about how it's going to affect our
practice. So previous journal clubs.
So I think we're up to about 70 now over
the last 6 1/2 years if we look at those
that we covered in July.
We see a heavy CSCC focus.
I'll color it in red here for all the CC
papers we've done previous July's over
the year. So back in 2019,
we did a prospective study of Sentinel to
the biopsy for high risk cutaneous SCC.
Very apropos for this month and take home
from this paper that was published in the
Head and Neck is that lymph node
metastases occur in 14% of patients with
high risk CSCC.
We'll see how that data compares to what
was found in this prospective clinical
trial in high risk patients as well.
Mhm.
Back in 2020 we did I think this JDS
paper targeted next generation sequencing
of matched localized and metastatic
primary high-risk CSCCS.
They studied gene mutations between
localized and metastatic SCCCS.
The intent of identifying key differences
in new potential targeted treatment
options wasn't necessarily groundbreaking
paper,
but I I'm curious just from the group
here today,
how frequently are people getting next
generation sequencing?
In their patients with CSCC,
do they get it up front if they get it?
Do they wait until they're at a post PD1?
What are some people's current practices
as far as NGS?
Vernon, I'll call you out.
What's your team's general approach these
I would say that interestingly,
the biggest place we tend to use NGS is
days?
diagnostically. Is it a cutaneous squeam?
Is it a squeam from some other source?
Is it a basal or a squamous cancer when
there's basalosquamous differentiation?
So looking, you know,
we've had some some really challenging.
Histopathology cases where just seeing
the large number of mutations in the
tumor and the predominant UV signature of
those mutations has has just ****.
Oh my gosh, well,
doesn't matter what it looks like and we
can go right.
To systemic immunotherapy and and quite a
few cases where there were some questions
of hedgehog inhibitor versus
immunotherapy, et cetera.
Sarcomatoid versus, you know,
sarcomatoid SEC versus sarcoma.
So I would say that has been the the big
place that we've used NGS is in that
diagnostic space,
even more so than therapeutic
decision-making,
although I'm sure there's.
Some things we can learn in the future of
where maybe immunotherapy versus say EGFR
targeted therapy,
are there signatures or or is there is
there hints at least?
Of which one will work and why in in
certain situations.
Perfect. Thanks Vernon.
And anyone else want to comment about NGS
and their local workflow real world for
CSCC Reed, what are you,
what are you guys doing at BI these days?
Well,
I would echo the comments made about
differentiating tumors that are difficult
to characterize by histopathology alone.
But I think we're not doing it in the
upfront setting for patients who have
localized or regionally metastatic
disease.
That, you know,
has been managed with surgery and
radiation with curative intent,
but we certainly are using it in patients
who have recurrent disease.
We may not be doing it before immune
checkpoint inhibitor therapy.
We may do it, you know,
a few cycles on if there is obviously no.
Response,
but we're definitely using that to
hopefully identify targetable gene
products.
We have a phase one program that you
participated in as well.
So we're always just trying to you know
look for.
Those options.
Perfect.
I would say it's very similar to MGH.
We use it less and less these days up
front.
I would say the lion's share of the IO we
get for CSCC is in the preoperative
M.
setting. So we don't do it there,
but we do do it if patients progress
target mutations or or T&
B for a certain trial eligibility as well.
I'm looking forward to 2021 from 2020.
We did the preprint of actually we didn't
that was before.
So this was a current medical research.
Where was this? What is this? Yeah,
this was a study looking at 40 GEP and
the integrating in NCC and guideline
recommendations for managing CSCC
patients,
publishing current medical research and
opinion.
Always a little bit of a controversial
subject. We actually talked about GP.
I think it was December. I think Brandon,
when you you did your research meeting
update for us,
GEP for us is used primarily now because
of the two papers looking at perhaps risk
stratifying.
Applying for benefit for adjuvant
radiation.
We've been using it a little bit more in
that setting,
but other than that we haven't been doing
a ton of GEP for CSCC. Curious,
anybody else using it for that risk
stratification for adjuvant therapy
benefit rate adjuvant radiation therapy
based on those two papers?
Nikhil, you're shaking your head.
Yeah,
but you have another way to save my
brother.
Spring.
It's a we use it as a rule out test when
we're looking to deescalate care,
so not to have a room in patients.
I'll fight your side and you discuss.
Got.
That's a good segue to the adjuvant
radiation paper we did 2022.
This was from Emily Ruiz.
This showed in their retrospective review
of Cleveland Clinic and BWH that adjuvant
radiation first claimed decreased the
risk of local regional recurrence.
by half,
kind of adding to the body of work about
radiation therapy. Again,
this group that's published a follow-up
study that showed it was only beneficial
in patients that were GEP class 2B.
And then two years ago,
we did the Annals of Surgical Oncology
paper looking at frequency
Of surveillance imaging for Melanoma
patients to take home there were more
frequent surveillance imaging for
patients for the resected Melanoma was
not associated with improved survival.
Sort of interesting study there.
And then today obviously we're going to
do CPOST. All right.
So that's the JC in review.
Just a quick comment on the perspective
on the science piece.
Our last piece was from our first open
meeting with BMS on Checkmate 358.
So again,
thank you to all for participating in
that.
I think that was our best perspective
piece to date.
And depending on how this conversation
goes today,
we'll probably do a follow up perspective
piece on today's topic as well. All right,
so let's get to the survey results. Again,
thank you for filling it out.
Just for Generon team, we always.
Do a survey last six months or so.
We've been sending out ahead of time on
just to get a sense of who's here and how
they're practicing germane to today's
topic.
So we had 25 respondents and we have a
nice mixture of specialists, Med Ox,
Serjon, Mose, Jen.
Derm or medical derms, APPs and trainees,
scientists and other CSC patient
experience, quite a big range,
but there are many of us that are seeing
quite a lot of squamous cell cancer.
Question about whether or not people have
recommended we've been part of a team of
recommending adjuvant anti PD1 to date
and about 13 percent, 13 respondents,
52% have recommended adjuvant anti PD1
immunotherapy.
Now I didn't ask this question,
but I'm curious.
Has anyone done that off trial or all 13
of the respondents like participants in
CPOST?
Has anyone used it off label to date?
So David,
I I assume the question was off protocol.
So I said no,
I'm actually it was gonna ask the
OK, OK. No, I yeah,
and he's open for interpretation.
question.
I'm curious about how do they get this
covered in the adjuvant setting here off
protocol.
I mean others might have,
others might have interpreted it as on
protocol.
So I think this question lacks that
specificity.
But either way there looks like there are
people who have experience.
Anyone want anyone who said yes want to
talk about their experience?
I I said no, David, but just like Nikhil,
I assume that's what you meant.
But I wonder if people are justifying
that as being, you know,
not completely resected and then calling
it not for the resectable and treating it
in there. So not a true adjuvant,
just a hypothesis.
Interesting.
I actually thought the two of you were in
the yes category when I saw this,
so I'm glad you guys spoke up. Anyone.
Anyone else who said yes?
Anyone here said yes.
Yes, for me, but just as on studies,
was that?
All right,
so we we have a clinical question here.
Clinical scenario.
This is a hypothetical situation.
71 year old male,
ECOG one's got a previous history of non
melanum skin cancer presents with a three
centimeter left parotid nodal medic CCC.
Patient is not interested in the clinical
trial, which is contrived,
but just to see kind of on, you know,
standard of care stuff,
what people would do.
So what would you or your MDCT likely
recommend?
The most common answer would start with
ICI and then reassess.
For surgery or radiation,
second most common answer was going
forward in the adjuvant approach and then
evaluating the path and making a response
treatment response assessment.
At that point,
8.
one person said they would do surgery
followed by adjuvant radiation adjuvant
immunotherapy.
The.
Comments or questions about this survey
question?
Burning. You got a smile on your face.
OK.
Yeah.
You're you're muted, Vern.
Yes. No, I was looking,
looking for the button. You know,
it's a little amusing,
not not interested in a clinical trial.
I understand what you're saying,
but this has been a particular area where
OK.
we have liked to use.
Neoadjuvant therapy both for Squame and
Merkel seems to be two situations where
we frequently will see presentation with
a parotid metastasis and the there's
really been quite a bit of benefit.
In in those patients and sometimes
avoiding surgery altogether with the with
the risks to the facial nerve.
So did you answer third up from the
bottom or the most bottom answer choice?
I I probably, I don't remember,
but I would probably have advocated to
Do you remember?
sort of the the third one,
start ICI and reassess after that what
what we would do next.
Kevin, what did you put? I'm curious.
Oh, definitely the neoadjuvant surgery.
Pathoval root cause you're you're
describing A resectable regional
metastasis and so I assume that people
who and I and I I don't know.
Um, start ICI reassess that most common.
Are people starting that as a definitive
And.
treatment?
I'll tell you. So I'll answer,
I'll answer where where my actual mental
Um.
thought process was.
So I initially had didn't have that throw
them up from the bottom.
I answered a neoadvent in my mind,
but then I'm like,
is that actually what we're doing these
days? Because more often than not,
like we're seeing the patient after two
And.
doses and we haven't taken people to
surgery like any recently.
Yeah.
Because they've had great responses or
they've had talks plus a response.
So I felt like third up from the bottom
was more faithful to how I'm actually.
You know, I'll just comment, Vern,
you had that editorial you wrote like a
I think.
couple years ago and I really thought
that that was spot on. You know,
Suzanne Tapalian's on this call too.
We did the neoadjuvant trial where you
formally are gonna get surgery no matter
what happens with your.
Facebook.
Immunotherapy after whatever, four weeks.
And that's not what we're doing at all.
Now we're doing what you called Verne
upfront immunotherapy and then you
basically wait and see. And I don't.
I I agree.
You know why put somebody's facial nerve
at risk And for this is for for cutaneous
squamous cell or Merkel.
If you just have this enormous response,
then you then you got the question of
well,
do you keep treating them forever with
immunotherapy? So that's a problem,
but and then it doesn't take advantage of
that. You don't get the pathologic data,
but if you have a just enormous.
E.
Clinical radiographic response.
We're not typically doing a big
dissection after that.
Perfect. Nikhil, I'll be back to Kevin.
Sorry.
Yeah. So what's fascinating about this is,
and actually in some ways a little
troubling as well,
is how far the pendulum has swung towards
neoadjuvant therapy or definitive therapy,
whichever way you call it,
because 68% of respondents admittedly
within a very niched group here have said
they would start with.
Upfront immunotherapy. Now this patient,
mind you,
would be a candidate for the current
Cooperative Group NRG study.
If we are already in this camp where we
feel neoadjuvant is so much better,
this is what we want to.
I wonder how much equipoise will still be
there for that study and will that study.
Survive, which is NRG 014.
So I think we would really need to sort
of go back and look is how are we going
to justify putting patients on that trial.
Nikhil,
tell us what that what happens in that
So it's randomization between sort of the
second last arm there minus the adjuvant
trial.
ACI.
So it's standard of care on that study is
still surgery followed by adjuvant
radiotherapy versus asking the question
neoadjuvant 4 cycles of cemiplimab
followed by.
Sort of risk adapted surgery.
The surgeon can decide whether to
Mhm.
de-escalate the operation that he or she
had originally planned plus RT,
but there's no adjuvant similimumab on
that surgical only arm.
So that's that's going to be a tough sell
if only 8% of folks are saying right now,
I mean 12% of folks are saying we would
give surgery followed by radiation plus
Mm-hmm.
minus ICI versus 68% neoadjuvant.
A.
And Nikhil, to your point,
we've discussed this with the Regeneron
OK.
team as well as one of the C post sites,
George Washington,
we we passed on that study after also
being a 1901 site for Neo Adjuvant
because that has become our standard
approach and we could not justify.
Yeah.
Yep.
enrolling patients or offering them that
option.
Kevin, you get another thought.
Your hand up.
You know,
this is one of the fun things about this
group is none of these answers quite fit
exactly how many of us feel,
OK.
in part because it's evolving so quickly.
See, David,
I would have thought you would have
skipped #3 because.
It says reassess for surgery or radiation
as opposed to give two cycles,
great response and no additional therapy.
Like the nuance here for us changes like
from month with each evolving month and
more experience.
And just hearing folks talk about their
experiences is what makes this moment so
fun,
because we've still got a lot to learn to
figure out the nuance.
And that's what this is about,
the nuance of this disease.
That allows us to give less treatment and
get better cures. This is good.
It's good. All right,
let's we could we could stay on this for
probably 20 minutes,
but let's March ahead here if we want to
get to the paper.
This is an interesting question.
This is kind of relevant to the paper,
right? So this this is a patient comes in,
you meet the patient after they've
already.
Had surgery and they come and talk about
the next steps.
So a patient's interested in adjuvants.
Miplamab saw the paper.
Question to the practitioners are how
comfortable are you using immunotherapy
in the absence of RT?
Like going straight to immunotherapy.
So nobody's very comfortable.
Six people are comfortable and then eight
people just not sure yet.
And two people are really uncomfortable.
And 16,
I mean four are uncomfortable comments
about.
These data and this question.
So 22 comments. One,
this scenario or a variant of it is way
Um.
too common in Merkel cell,
I mean in in cutaneous squamous cell and
that is that.
People who have nodal involvement,
you know it isn't synchronous nodal
involvement, right?
They're not showing up with a big tumor
and a big lymph node.
They've had Mohs surgery six times over
the last 12 years.
And suddenly they've got a lymph node in
the parotid and whoever they or the
axilla or fill in the blank,
wherever it is.
And the practitioner who evaluates the
lymph node doesn't even consider the fact
that they've had skin cancers in the past
as relevant to the differential.
Sends them to a surgeon who just says, oh,
this,
this node has to come out and the
opportunity to do neoadjuvant with all
the advantages we just talked about in
the previous cases is out the window.
So it's it's still all too common that
these squamous patients show up to us
with a scar instead of measurable disease.
They can have neoadjuvant therapy,
which means there's always going to be a
role.
Potentially for adjuvant systemic therapy.
I think I signed up for ambivalent in the
in the truest sense of the word.
I'm torn in two directions. I want to.
I know that the better.
That that adjuvant systemic therapy is
potentially valuable for this case.
I think it could potentially decrease the
need for radiation, but.
The ambivalent part is we don't have the
data,
we don't have the FDA approval and we
have trials that required radiation, not.
Trials that did what we want to do,
which is eliminate radiation if you give
systemic immunotherapy.
Totally agree. Ross, you had your hand up.
I was just gonna thank you for putting
this question in because I think it
really gets at,
I think the crux of and I don't want to
jump too far ahead,
but like I think it gets at the crux of
like how do we decide to incorporate
these data into our practice?
Do we think the radiation in between
surgery and immunotherapy has a
biological role for why adjuvant
immunotherapy is helpful or?
You know, and so,
so I think it it just really gets at this,
this, this question.
I think that we're we're all gonna face
time and time again when we see someone
who's in between surgery,
who's immediately after surgery but
hasn't yet had radiation.
And we have to decide if we really want
to recommend they actually get radiation
before we're willing to give them unit
therapy.
I think it's going to be challenging,
but and I think I put uncomfortable,
but I mean,
I fall exactly into the camp that Vernon.
You know, described, I think. Uh,
it's just where I ended up, uh,
being pulled through more,
but I have the same same exact thought
process.
Well,
I I think I had you in mind when I wrote
the question because I felt like you
asked the same question what,
three or four weeks ago at tumor board.
So and based on their response then I'm
not surprised you put uncomfortable,
which is totally reasonable. All right,
let's final graphic. Oh,
and actually this is great. All right,
looking into.
The future roughly one year or so.
Do you think your team's going to be
doing anti PD1 therapy more in the
adjuvant or neoadjuvant setting?
The answer speaks for itself.
All right,
and then barriers for implementing anti
PD1 in the adjuvant setting. Pretty mixed,
but using neoadjuvant most common of the
checkbox answers is select all that apply.
People concerned about toxicity,
uncertain benefit versus risk of the
toxicity.
Preparing to wait for recurrence to avoid
overtreatment selected by 6 people.
Any comments?
I would just say that in the rubric of
toxicity concerns,
it subsumes the fact that a big barrier
to adjuvant therapy is the
immunosuppressed patient,
the transplant patient.
Mhm.
The patient with autoimmunity, you know,
not just the usual toxicities,
but the specific patients who who we
would have to exclude typically from
adjuvant therapy.
Are are some of the patients who need it
the most and that's a barrier that we
will face even after FDA approval.
Good point.
Can I ask a quick question here, David?
I'm I'm really curious about #3 cost or
Yeah, of course.
insurance because I'm wondering why that
was chosen by some individuals if this
was an FDA approved agent for high risk
CSCC.
And I'm wondering if similar decisions
are made for Melanoma as well.
Others wanna chime in?
No, Nikhil, I think I I probably checked.
I checked off a whole bunch here,
OK.
but I I guess just being a little bit
trying to be a good steward of healthcare
and if I'm not 100% convinced of its role
and.
It's really costly for a large subset of
patients that aren't going to benefit
from it.
So that was my that was that was my
concern.
Not all insurance companies will
necessarily cover it,
even if it's FDA approved.
Satisfying answer, Nikhil.
Well, I'm just curious.
It's not an issue of satisfying me.
Yeah.
I'm just curious about the perspective is,
you know,
I I am definitely a steward of making
sure that we remain cost effective.
I would have loved for a trial to have
six months of therapy rather than 12
months of therapy because we have no idea
what the true duration of treatment here
is.
But I was just curious to see, you know,
what is driving some of these decisions
as to whether we would or would not be
utilizing this form of treatment in high
risk situations. Now admittedly,
the example that I gave of Melanoma is
quite different. I mean,
most of these patients who recur tend to
still recur.
With local regional disease rather than
distant metastatic disease,
whereas Melanoma it could be quite
different.
Certainly with Merkel it would be very
different as well.
But I I mean these these questions what I
I think David that you put down are so
thought provoking.
So I applaud you on that too.
Yeah, thank you.
And I think it'd be interesting if you
actually rank ordered it.
Cost insurance would probably be pretty
Oh.
low,
but it's still it's still something that
Yeah.
goes through my head as well.
I think I was one that also checked off
that and it goes with the overtreatment
question. Like if you're gonna,
I don't know,
we can look at the numbers if out of 100
people 83.
Gonna recur. I'm sorry.
Ethan are not gonna recur. And you know,
from a local regional perspective,
then there's a lot of overtreatment and
that costs the system a lot if the person
never needed it because they were cured
by the radiation oncologist and surgical
oncologist. All right.
And then I think our last one is an
alluvial plot.
S.
So I'll just zoom in here for people who.
Who you know, don't look at these.
This allows you to sort of just track
each individual response like who says
what.
And this is this is kind of a cool then
idea.
I don't know what came up with the
alluvial plot,
but it's it's it's pretty awesome but
takes a little takes a little while to
kind of absorb.
What's going on here?
But you can basically track like each
individual and who's you know,
who's thinking what and recommending what
from a specialty perspective.
Starts from a specialty perspective and
tracks the responses across the questions.
So we have one Med OC who says in the
future they think they're going to use
more adjuvant therapy.
I don't know if that person's on the call,
but I would be kind of interested in
hearing that person's perspective.
All right, maybe they're not on the call.
All right. Anyway,
I think this will be this might be a nice
figure for for a follow-up paper because
it does take a little time to sort of
absorb and process all the information.
But that is our intro before the actual
intro of the paper. Kevin,
do you want to you want to take it away?
Sure.
So we've set some ground for this study
and and our conversation of, you know,
the the control arm in this study is what
is considered at the time the study
started.
Of common practice or standard of care,
which is surgery followed by radiation
therapy.
We know that there are a subset of
patients with high risk local tumors,
high risk of local recurrence,
high risk of regional recurrence,
a very small subset with a risk of
distant.
Metastasis,
but because so much of it is local
recurrence, regional recurrence,
our local therapies of surgery and
radiation have long been how we've taken
care of these patients.
And yet we know that's still a fairly
unsatisfying approach.
Um to how we care for these patients
which?
Leads to the potential role for a more
systemic treatment,
as well as something that is perhaps more
effective than radiation in particular
and might be have a broader field than
surgery and radiation.
Can offer.
This study tries to ask the question,
if we add in cemiplimab on top of surgery
and radiation, can we improve?
The outcome for these patients and it's,
you know,
it's a study that focuses on two
different groups.
One are locally advanced primaries,
locally advanced resectable primaries.
So that means patients with AT4 lesion.
With clinical PNI, thanks David,
meaning involving a named cranial nerve,
a patient with a local recurrence plus
one other high risk feature,
meaning at least a T3 or poorly
differentiated or greater than two
centimeters.
Or an in transit.
And I think that's a pretty easy group
that everybody would agree is a high risk
for recurrence even after surgery and
radiation.
And then a group of regional lymph node
metastasis that has ECS.
As well as greater than two centimeters
or three or more lymph nodes.
And I know David's kind of highlighting
some of these different studies,
but focusing on this study or this slide,
sorry,
highlights that I think everybody agrees
this is a,
this is the patient population that we
worry about.
With both surgery and with radiation
therapy.
So study looks at randomizing patients to
immunotherapy in the form of Semiplimab
after surgery and radiation for 10 more
months.
Initially every three weeks and then
every six weeks. Um.
This study happens in the setting of the
end of our neoadjuvant studies.
At this point, as this study is enrolling,
we are finishing the accrual and learning
more and more about neoadjuvant.
And so this study is also tough timing
wise because our common practice starting
to shift while we start to explore this
role as well in terms of big picture of
how we manage these patients.
So maybe I'll pause there, David.
Perfect. I will just add also that this,
this paper comes, you know,
highly anticipated because over the last
year, you know,
we've received various pieces of
information. So you know, in August,
almost a year ago,
we get a press release that 630 is going
to be shut down due to futility.
And then in January,
we get a press release that says, wow,
some implement is associated with 68%
reduction in DFS. So for a while,
you know, for six months or so,
we weren't sure how to reconcile these
two.
And I'm not sure we're going to get any
reconciliation today. But yeah,
I would say like this study I'm really
looking forward to get.
To more of the discussion,
but this is also part of the backdrop is
we had two very similar studies with
presumably very similar agents that had
pretty disparate results from Lisa press
release.
There are nuances that I think make it a
little less.
Disparate,
but still nevertheless we have a positive
study and a negative study from kind of
traditional frequent statistics
perspective. Vishal,
you have your hand up.
Thanks, David.
Thanks again for doing the intro and
filling in for me.
Sorry for treating my responsibilities.
Those don't know made a last minute plan
for my son's 9th birthday,
Yeah.
so apologies for being in the car.
I I just want to give some historical
perspective because I think it's
important a lot of people on the call
here may not have.
Add a touch point on this and what I
wanted to provide is Matthew Fury said
that he has been at Regeneron for 10
years and I think it's mindful for us to
know that this trial has been a work for
about 10 years,
maybe shortly right after he joined,
shortly after he finished,
I finished training.
So it's been a long time coming in.
During that time,
the idea of neoadjuvant hadn't come in.
And it's important to know that this is a
global trial. And so a lot of discussion,
at least in the US and what we discussed
early on this call around the role of
radiation is a challenging one.
Where across the world there's a lot of
different approaches and and and this was
a cooperative group led by the Tasmanian
Radiation Oncology Group.
So there is a big historical piece of
understanding why radiation was was
paramount at that time .
89 years ago and we've learned a lot in
the last decade.
But that's that's an important piece to
think about how that was an important
role at that time point.
And how do we how do we interpret that
now?
I will also add some historical
commentary around the 630 trial,
as well as this trial,
that those those risk features that Kevin
so eloquently explained is
Really what we worry about the most is
not pulled out of thin air,
but really is based on a variety of
papers that show that the risk of
recurrence appears to be the highest in
those nodal and extra nodal risk factors.
And when we compared that to Keynote 630
for anybody who considered opening both
those trials.
There is some difference between the two
and that's been the challenging to
concern when these trials first enrolled
was if we had two positive studies or two
negative or in this case a negative or
positive,
how are we going to interpret that?
I'm actually hopeful now having seen the
presentation to ask on curious to see
what the discussion is here,
my interpretation being that it has
provided some clarity to me.
On where there is a potential role and
benefit and similar to what Vernon said,
I also see this as now provides us with a
lot of opportunity for our patients,
gives us a shared decision making of what
makes sense or what is what card is
handed to us,
what cards are dealt to us when the
patient presents either early on.
or potentially after therapy is done.
So I think things have come around not
the way we anticipated and there was a
lot of consternation around getting this
trial going.
It opened before neoadjuvant and it took
a long time to complete after.
But I think we've learned a lot more than
we anticipated now.
Excited to hear that discussion about
that.
Thank you, Shah. Agreed. Agreed. Well,
let's dive into the papers.
We can go pretty quickly through it
because I don't think it's that hard to
digest and then leave some room to really
talk about how we're going to, you know,
integrate this into our practice and and
why we think the two studies may be
different. Reid,
do you want to just give us a quick
overview of who participated in this
study?
From a patient perspective.
Yeah,
I think the characteristics summarized in
this table are pretty well balanced
between the two arms.
It's an older age population,
which is not surprising.
Male greater than female, not surprising.
Mostly white, not surprising.
And lesser representation in North
America than.
Australia,
New Zealand and the rest of the world,
excellent performance status of 0 to one
and 80% you know these patients had head
and neck high risk squamous cell cancers.
I think getting to the the issue of this
is really a high risk population,
there's no question about it so.
If you wanted to show a difference
between Semiplimab versus placebo,
this is how you could design the study.
Very high risk disease and a lot of nodal
disease and 50 of the patients had
extracapsular extension. So that's pretty,
pretty amazing.
The perineural invasion,
as Kevin pointed out,
is defined by a major nerve that's
impacted,
not not microscopic perineural invasion.
And you know, I think,
I think the the PD-L1 status is
interesting and as you'll see on some
some of the subsequent.
Results,
it doesn't really play much of A role in
terms of whether patients respond or not.
So I think you know this,
I think the take home message is,
is that this clearly is a high risk
population.
Thank you, Reed. You know,
I don't know the Regeneron team,
I don't know if Matthew or Frank want to
tackle this.
I am curious about the geographic
representation.
Was this something you guys might have
anticipated that the port showing so to
speak from North America or did that take
you by surprise?
And I guess I'll say that in the context
of, you know, like.
It.
We opened the study at Mass General
because in 2020, whenever 2019, you know,
we thought this was a great fit for our
program.
As Kevin and Vishal spoke to the
neoadjuvant study,
we also opened and sort of shifted our
practice and we ended up,
we know we had this trial open for three
or four years as Chris knows and we
didn't enroll anybody.
So I don't know if that was a.
Experience across North America or just
fewer sites opened or did sites open like
we did and just not a crew?
So I guess you know from the beginning
even in advance the ACC,
you know number of patients enrolled at a
site in Australia is like higher than
anywhere else in the world.
So we knew we would kind of lead the way
as you as I think Vishal alluded to
before it was also.
Done in collaboration with the with the
Trog.
So you know there was just early on a lot
of buy in there.
The other thing that Vishal mentioned is
that this day was actually designed in
2017 and then the new adjuvant study was
in 2019 and I think.
In the USII think, you know,
there was more adoption of just, you know,
new adjuvant use. And I think that's why,
you know,
some of the major centers in the US,
you know,
didn't put a lot of patients on the study.
So yeah,
I think my answer to your question is
maybe just kind of coming back to some of
the points that Vishal and Vishal and
others have made.
Perfect. Thank you, Matthew. So, Vernon,
you got your hand up.
Yes, and I was just.
Wanted to 1st echo the comment that this
is a really high risk patient population
ideal for addressing the question,
but do we?
Has anyone seen comparable data from the
keynote study at this level? My right?
And in the in the ASCO presentation,
the slide went just ****,
went by in in a millisecond and didn't
break it down at this level at all.
And so you know when we get that data,
when we get the equivalent.
It is really going to be important to to
put tables together and show if we can,
how many people were in each of these
categories and how many people in the
keynote trial.
Would not have been eligible for this
trial.
We're in categories that that wouldn't
have fit because these are the things
we're going to have to understand now and
as we'll talk about it in the in the
conclusions.
Maybe we're going to hear echoes of this
very phenomenon in the future,
but clearly a high-risk thing.
The one thing I still don't understand
about cutaneous squamous cell cancer,
maybe you experts can help me understand.
How does the cancer know the name of the
nerve? Or if the nerve has a name,
how does it?
No.
Question for smarter,
smarter people than me as well, Vernon.
Kevin.
Yeah, that's great.
Perfect. All right,
let's keep trucking through. Nikhil,
do you want to kind of take the the main
slide punchline slide?
Sure. Just to remind everyone,
so this was a randomization between
adjuvant cimiplimab initially at the
standard FDA approved dose 350 milligrams
every three weeks for up to one year of
therapy.
And then there was a protocol amendment
that permitted or changed the adjuvant
dosing to every three weeks for 12.
12 weeks and then every six weeks at 700
milligrams,
all the remainder of the one year balance.
And the primary endpoint here was disease
free survival and disease free being.
Defined as essentially recurrence of
disease or death from any cause,
disease or non disease related.
The hypothesis here was that on the
control arm, the placebo arm,
the three-year disease free survival was
going to be 55%.
Remember correctly and this was based on
the high risk subgroup analysis from the
TROG study that as many of you recall was
an adjuvant trial of radiotherapy with or
without weekly carboplatin.
And within that group one of the defined
subgroups or high risk groups was.
Patients with a lymph node size of 22mm
with evidence of extracapsular extension
and their five year DFS was 56%.
So this was the placebo arm here and as
you can clearly see,
the arms separate early.
A win in this study was considered to be
a hazard ratio of 0.
6 and there were three pre specified
interim analysis based on timing of
events and at the first interim analysis
was when.
The boundary for futility was crossed and
so this was declared to be a positive
study.
Median follow up I believe was about 24
months.
So you can clearly see the number of
events on the experimental cimiplumab arm
was 24 placebo 65 hazard ratio of 0.32.
And a highly statistically significant P
value and that seems the curve seem to
sort of be maintaining their separation
and the Kaplan Meier estimation method.
And a hazard ratio of 0.
32 is about as low as we see across all
the diseases we treat, is it not?
It is.
I think the only one that came close or
somewhere there was when Georgina Long
presented the Checkmate 78 data for
Yeah.
adjuvant stage 2B2C nivolumab to my
recollection that was at SMR probably
three years ago or somewhere around that
time.
And that was somewhere in the same range,
but overtime that that has changed and
sort of become very similar to the
Keynote 716 trial as well.
Perfect. All right, let's keep going.
Ross,
do you wanna look at the subgroups or
just give us an editorial on your take on
the subgroups?
Yeah, I mean,
I think the big take home here is that in
more or less every subgroup analysis,
you know the results favored Semiplimab
with the few lines that are crossing one
kind of,
I think potentially just being
attributable to a small sample size given.
The actual, you know,
value favors Semiplimab,
but the confidence interval just kind of
just gets over one a little bit.
One one thing potentially that I think
maybe is a little bit interesting even
though this is a small samples like in
the, you know in the non-white population,
you know are those biologically different.
A.
Tumors. But again,
it's a small sample size,
really hard to draw conclusions.
And there did seem to be some sort of
trend for people who were older deriving
more benefit.
You know,
I'm not really sure if that if there's
really true biological significance there.
The other two things I would point out
here are that PD L1,
as we have seen in prior studies of skin
cancer and was recapitulated.
And this study also did not have any
association between response or you know
benefit or non-benefit.
And then the last thing is that there
were too few patients with with CLL to
really comment on whether CLL would have
had an impact on you know that would have
been.
Good to see you know kind of I, I, I, I,
I forget who was commenting on on this
element earlier might have been Vern
about you know we we often see patients
who are who are immunosuppressed and I
applaud some you know the Regeneron team.
For for including patients with CLL on
this protocol.
But I do think that you know the fact
that there weren't enough patients in the
study to really assess that does
highlight the need for this to be an area
of future study given we see so many of
patients with immunosuppressed conditions
that are their primary driving factor for
why they have so many cutaneous claims.
Thank you, Ross. Isaac,
do you want to tell us about the local
regional recurrence and distant
recurrence data?
Sure.
So Figure 3 is is explores 2 secondary
endpoints that look at the different
flavors of disease free survival.
This is something that you can do
effectively.
When you ended up overpowering your study
by so much,
the effect size is so big and we're
seeing in the subgroup analysis that
we're still finding significance.
Same thing is seen here as we just saw in
the forest plot.
That local,
if you look at just local regional
recurrence events,
despite there being very few of them,
you see a nice hazard ratio that's,
you know, very small.
When I look at these Kaplan Meier curves,
it's the, you know, the the thumb rule,
right?
If you hold your thumb up at arm's length.
length and it fits between the curves,
then then it's a good study.
And even on these, you know,
subgroup analyses, secondary endpoints,
your thumb readily fits between the
curves. I don't know what we can,
what we can really learn about.
The nature of these recurrences in the
biology of local regional versus distant
recurrences,
they both have beneficial effect from
getting the adjuvant drug.
And this is the distant recurrence. Again,
nice hazard ratio. Curves are separate.
And then Sameer, are you on?
You wanna just finish the data with a
quick review of the adverse events?
Yeah, sounds like, you know,
basically the adverse event in the
Similipomat group was 91% and the placebo
group was 89%.
The most common adverse events were
fatigue and pruritus, rash and diarrhea.
It sounded like, you know, 9.
8% of patients ended up discontinuing
treatment in the cemiplimab arm and then
basically 1.5% on the placebo arm.
They made a comment in the text that 22%
in the cemiplimab arm experience
immune-related.
Did adverse events, whereas only 6.
4% getting placebo did,
which I thought was kind of interesting.
And yeah,
basically I think the general take home
was that the adverse event or the side
effect profile of the simliptimab arm was
sort of similar to the data from
metastatic.
Trials.
Agreed. Thank you, Sameer. All right,
I'm gonna put this in the chat.
This is a quick survey for.
Go ahead.
One question about whether or not this is
going to change your practice.
You guys click on it and respond.
It'll be great. But in the meantime,
while people are doing that,
it is getting close to the hour.
I I I think this is going to be.
A fairly provocative discussion,
so I appreciate if people need to leave
because it's 4:00, please just sign out.
For those that want to stay and engage in
conversation,
we'll keep the forum open for a bit.
It's just our way.
We tend to have a lot to say over over
the hour.
Often goes over a little bit.
So with that, Kevin, do you want to,
I know you did the intro,
but if you have a few words you want to
start with and then we can just open it
up to general discussion.
And I think this is a a really
experienced group with in terms of the
roles of immunotherapy and all of
cutaneous oncology.
Like look across this group,
we have experience in cutaneous squamous
cell, Merkel cell, Melanoma,
a really robust experience and.
A lot of those other experiences help
inform in part how I think about some of
this data as well.
And I'm wondering for this group,
you know,
one of the things that stands out as in
the Melanoma data in particular,
for example, the adjuvant trials focus.
On disease free survival and for a number
of different reasons,
both design as well as interim analysis,
stopping early,
some of those kinds of things,
we've yet to see an overall survival
benefit in the adjuvant setting and I
wonder.
I pose to this group.
Do you think there will be an overall
survival advantage in this group and?
Does it matter for you in terms of how
you will incorporate this into your
practice?
Who wants to go first?
In the interest of time,
I suggest we throw some things into chat
too,
because that can be a fast way to because
we really are out of time here.
Perfect, Paul. Thank you. That's a good,
good suggestion for sure.
Yeah.
Do people think there's gonna be no S
benefit? I mean,
I know there's there was a little bit of
data has hasn't been fully mature,
hazard ratio favoring,
but confidence intervals wide or crossing
the traditional mull.
So Paula,
is your comment to suggest that yes,
that is important because if it shows an
overall survival,
you're going to be much more inclined to
recommend it.
And if we don't see an overall survival
benefit, you're going to be less inclined.
Can you articulate that?
Yeah, definitely. You know,
sometimes the recurrence isn't the end of
the world. You know, the simple, you know,
we may be able to rescue that person.
And I don't, I don't know. I mean,
it's it's super hard to design the trial
that way, right? Because it means,
you know,
afterwards maybe we have better therapies
down the line and it's really,
it's really messy.
You know another high level question I
had is are we saying in the United States
maybe a lot of these patients wouldn't be
eligible for adjuvant cause they wouldn't
be getting surgery up front,
they'd be getting neo neo adjuvant
immunotherapy.
Is that kind of am I getting that that
and that might be different in Australia,
I don't know.
That is, that is, yeah,
that's my message is that most of our
patients are gonna get that come in with
this criteria and especially the nodals
are gonna get up front preoperative.
But but exactly, Vern, as you said,
if it somewhat disappointingly,
if they come in with a scar instead of a
gaping node,
this is super relevant data then, right?
It's very relevant.
It will definitely inform our
conversation.
There are going to be many patients,
I think that we elect to say we're going
to watch you closely.
First sign of recurrence,
we will treat you.
I think that's going to be a common
clinical scenario,
but we'll have this conversation.
I imagine this will be on label,
so we'll be able to say that in 2026.
I wonder if anybody,
as you were hearing David say that there
will be, you know,
groups and a lot of people who will say,
you know what,
we're just going to watch you and treat
upon recurrence.
One of the downsides of that that is
different than Melanoma in particular.
Is the morbidity that comes from a local
recurrence in particular?
And does that play into anybody's
thinking to to say, you know what,
Yep.
hygiene treatment might actually be more
meaningful?
Because of maybe it's not overall
survival,
but from Disease Control and limiting
morbidity from recurrence.
Would anybody ascribe to that argument?
I would definitely agree with that
because a lot of these patients,
despite adjuvant radiotherapy,
often will recur relapse right in the
surgical bed and very quickly.
And those patients, yes,
while we could still potentially salvage
them.
After they have developed macroscopic
relapse,
I think this paper shows us that there
were fewer local regional recurrences
with everything else being equal.
In other words,
both groups of patients received
appropriate local therapy, yet there were.
Noticeably lower local recurrences in the
adjuvant simiplumab army and I think
that's really important in this group of
patients because many of them
unfortunately will succumb to
uncontrolled regional disease and not
always metastatic disease.
But do you think biologically it is going
to be more effective to give cemiplimab
when there's microscopic disease than
early macro? I mean,
that's the fundamental question, right?
Like if it's biologically more effective,
it makes sense to give,
even though they're going to be many
patients, many they're going to be.
Half the patients that you know you give
it to that never needed it. You feel like,
yeah, if I catch it early,
biologically it's probably going to be
the same.
Either they have the T cells or they
don't or you know the micro environment
is is more suitable when it's micro than
macro.
I mean that's that's what it comes down
to, right?
Oh, so.
Like,
I don't know if that's a compelling
argument.
Like I I hope somebody can make that
compelling argument why like the micro
would be more responsive than the macro
other than like clonal fine clonal
heterogeneity as you get a collection of
cells and maybe some become resistant,
they lose whatever.
Oh.
Epitelle that would have made them target,
but.
Yeah.
I think in some way. Oh, sorry. Yeah,
David,
if in some ways the overall survival
benefit will as long as patients in the
placebo arm were are treated with
immunotherapy at the relapse setting,
the survival benefit will tell us a
little bit about that because I think
that most would treat upon relapse.
IO upfront and if if you don't detect a
survival benefit,
then those patients were salvaged.
And if you do,
then clearly there's some benefit to
treating upfront,
whether it's because patients deteriorate
quickly or what.
But I think that will be the the question
that.
The overall survival answered.
Suzanne, you have your hand up.
I think don't we need to know if this is
cancer specific survival.
So you know the issue for these patients
is similar to Merkel cell.
It's an older patient population and
they're more likely to die of cardiac
disease and other causes.
So I think we really need to know if this
is cancer specific survival that we're
talking about and not not all the the
studies really address that.
Just another general comment,
I mean I I find it interesting that.
This group seems to be making many
assumptions based on maybe the the
Melanoma studies where it that's the only
place where neoadjuvant was randomized
against adjuvant.
And also that nobody has discussed
whether if you give neoadjuvant,
should you also give adjuvants,
should you have those two phases.
Now there are several approvals right now
from the FDA and and outside US
regulators.
For neoadjuvant plus adjuvant,
for lung cancer, for bladder cancer,
head and neck cancer, breast cancer,
they all give neoadjuvant plus adjuvant.
The the only approval that doesn't have
an adjuvant phase with neo.
Is the first lung cancer approval and I
think now people are all giving adjuvant
in lung cancer rather than just Neo.
So I I'd like to hear and and maybe from
the folks at Regeneron.
Are any head-on trials being planned
comparing neoadjuvant versus adjuvant and
cutaneous squam?
And is it being considered that
cemiplimab should be continued in the
adjuvant phase after Neo?
So we don't have any sponsored studies
asking that question.
I know the NRG study also does not have
that design right now,
but obviously in light of these data,
they're having discussions. So we'll see,
you know if that study provides some data
on that.
I would say from the initial new adjuvant
study, I mean.
The investor initiated study that Neil
Gross did,
you know it's only 20 patients and then
the phase two still about 79 patients,
single arm studies and we continue to
follow those patients and have a lot of
patients accumulating a lot right is
irrelevant because there.
Small studies,
but a sizable portion of patients there
who were PCR's and were just observed and
continue to do well.
So it really does in this disease is
maybe the paradigm of immune responsive
tumor kind of put the question to the
fore.
You know is a patient who has a PCR are
they done and you know really done like a
lot of those patients had no radiation.
Therapy Niagra, Simipumab,
they were truly done,
OK.
but we don't have that.
You know what you're asking for, which is,
you know,
a large randomized trial developed,
you know,
being developed by the company to answer
it.
The closest thing might be the
cooperative group study.
And I will say, Suzanne, you know,
our experience and I'm sure I'm curious
what others is like in this particular
disease,
the patients that get upfront therapy and
have a very impressive response, they do.
They've done very well over the last five
years where we've really implemented this
as part of our practice.
Like I have no appetite to give them any
additional.
Adjuvant immunotherapy.
I feel like we would be putting them at
increased risk of harm cost to the system.
We just have had excellent. I mean,
Great.
our experience has mirrored what the
study showed very few, if any,
index tumor recurrences.
Or they're distant from what we thought
was the index tumor. Yes,
they developed new primaries and things,
but our experience has been very good,
so I have no appetite.
David, can you,
can you talk more about that?
That's after two cycles and if they have
a.
That has been our approach the last two
years. Kevin,
would you say 2 cycles is really what we
kind of migrated to? Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that's right.
And and that's if a complete clinical and
radiologic response,
you forego surgery and radiation at that
point or?
Kevin, you wanna? You can. Yeah,
feel free to.
You know, I think we are evolving Isaac.
I think we started with a a very strict
new adjuvant definition and we gave 2
cycles and they went to surgery.
And I think over time and seeing some
other groups talk about this a little bit
too, we've.
Started to say, gosh,
if you have a really,
really robust response,
maybe it's two cycles. And then we,
I think David coined the term slow
medicine where we're just going to walk
really slowly before we do anything else,
whether it's surgery.
Or more immunotherapy.
And in the last couple months,
we've maybe moved to that direction even
more. Unfortunately,
I can't tell you what that's going to
look like two or five years from now,
but we do have.
We have several hints of that, right?
That it's going to be OK.
Burning your hand up.
So a few comments about, excuse me,
everything we've heard. One,
if you take a step back and.
Maybe not so much recently,
but a year ago in our tumor boards when
we talked about doing neoadjuvant therapy
for a potentially resectable squamous
cell cancer, our radiation oncologists.
Who are great partners and great team
members would always chime in and say you
know you are introducing systemic therapy
here to a patient who has a standard of
care option.
For surgery and radiation that wouldn't
have any of these systemic toxicities and.
Cost and inconveniences, et cetera.
And so and it was a strong argument in
Melanoma.
We were going to give these people a year
of immunotherapy after the fact.
So giving them two doses before or three
doses before.
Was very easy to sell.
Now obviously this data shows that
systemic therapy is good afterward.
The Melanoma trials told us that actually
adjuvant therapy maybe isn't as good as
neoadjuvant therapy, right?
That what you were talking about, David,
of micromets.
Being treated early is somehow beneficial.
No,
we we think that that it's too late to
treat at this point after the primary and
the main tumor burden has been removed.
It would be interesting if we could do a
swog.
1801 trial with this exact patient
population and redo it.
And would the would neoadjuvant
cemiplimab for three doses be better than
all of cemiplimab post?
Operatively, but you know,
it's remarkable that we've got this kind
of hazard ratios with post-operative
therapy, with immunotherapy,
recognizing that.
But I also want to go back to this issue
of.
Waiting for a survival advantage. Oh,
we can salvage these patients.
The same people are benefiting.
And I'll I'll return to a metaphor that I
used in the early days of interferon.
So there's a big difference between
rescue and salvage.
Rescue is when your boat is about to go
over Niagara Falls and a helicopter
swoops in and picks you out of that boat
before it goes over the edge.
Maybe picks you up and the boat and takes
you both off before it goes over the edge.
Salvage is when you're waiting at the
bottom of Niagara Falls to pick up as
many of the pieces as you can,
and even if you put the whole boat back
together.
Right. You were not.
You were disadvantaged big time by going
over the falls.
Think about this slide we're looking at
that 30% or so of people who had a local
regional recurrence on the placebo arm.
That wasn't just any old local regional
recurrence that you could easily resect.
That's a recurrence in a radiated field,
right? In many of these patients,
most of the time on the scalp where
you're going to talk about a really
morbid.
Situation if you can salvage it.
So I for one am not thinking about
survival as the goal here.
This is to make sure this elderly patient
population.
Doesn't die with uncontrolled disease,
even if they die from something else.
And so, so from my perspective,
that's really compelling.
But the last point that I want to make is
when you look at all of this data,
the curves that we've seen.
The forest plots and how absolutely
consistently those dots line up in every
case on the correct side of the dotted
line. And I challenged any of you. I said,
OK, here's the challenge.
I want you to redo this clinical trial.
But you have to make it come out as a
negative study.
What are you going to do?
Redo the study and give me a negative
result. You'd say, Oh my gosh,
that would be really hard to do, right?
This is so beneficial.
How am I going to make it a negative
study?
You would have to include so many people
who are a low risk.
To wash out the the benefit of.
Such a powerful therapy.
So it's going to be really important to
understand why we have two trials.
Of course,
our bias is that the trial that had the
wonderful positive result is the right
trial and the one that had the bad result
is.
The wrong trial,
and I absolutely believe that,
but we ought to be scientific enough to
really make sure we understand whether
that's the case or not,
and most importantly.
I believe that in some point in the
future we are going to have this exact
same discussion.
Why did this adjuvant Merkel cell trial
show up so positive and this adjuvant
Merkel cell show up totally negative?
And we're going to have the same thing
deja vu all over again with Merkel cell.
That's that has been my prediction since
the day we heard these results.
We'll see if it occurs and.
And trial design is really,
really important, but it is remarkable,
as as strong as these results are,
that that you could reverse engineer them
into results that weren't as favorable.
So Vernon,
a couple of comments because there's,
Yeah.
I guess there are multiple hypotheses
that you could generate to explain what
you just said. The first one,
I think the one that you really are
pushing forward is that there's something
different about the risk groups.
So if we look at this study here.
Right. Keynote 630.
I think what you're saying is like
they're the placebo group is not going to
not going to recur as frequently because
they are a lower risk than C post.
Now we're going to just do some
hypothesis generating because this is
cross trial stuff.
This is not a match adjusted indirect
comparison, so we can't do that but.
If you look at the two placebo groups,
they're not that different.
They're not so like this,
this like we got to wait for the data to
see like we have,
we have some data right here to make some
some hypothesis generator.
We're not going to come to any firm
conclusions,
but these groups aren't that different,
right? three-year, 63 versus 60.
So that's one hypothesis.
Anyone want to make an argument for this
hypothesis?
That the drugs are just different, right?
I mean, again, Matt,
it's not a mass adjust.
I didn't do any mass adjusting here.
We could mean a potentially do that down
the road. But it is, you know,
it's it's interesting. Maybe, I mean,
I don't know, this is these are the,
these are the four curves overlaid.
Between the two studies,
because these are all reconstructed
individual patient data,
so they're not perfect.
They're they're pretty good,
but they're not. They're not 100%.
I didn't get the data from the studies I
had recreated them myself.
But no, it's it's interesting.
What what do people,
what do people think of given the
survival course and and given not only
the survival course, but the inclusion,
the inclusion exclusion criteria,
they're like not that different when they
they are very nuanced differences between
them.
Oh.
Was was there a difference in how much
radiation was given um post operatively
between the two trials, David?
You know,
I don't know if we know the full day.
There is again some differences.
I think I remember seeing Kevin Harris
It was.
and I said like 56 versus 60 to higher.
But you know, I I don't,
I don't know the dispersion like I don't
really know how it all worked out,
Yes.
M.
That was one difference and I think the
other difference, David,
but I we.
was the timing to randomization following
radiation.
There was a longer time on the keynote
study relative to the CPOS study,
so it took a longer time.
There's like 2 to 10 versus 4 to 16 I
think is the difference. C post C to 10.
Something like that. Yeah. Yep, Yep.
So we're you know a a a few weeks again.
So there are there are multiple
Right.
hypotheses you can generate,
one being different risk groups,
radiation makes a difference.
The dose makes a difference.
But again, all those things,
if you look at the, you know,
I I would.
both these groups got radiation,
both these groups, you know,
basically had the same time.
They're not that different from at least
a placebo looking at the baseline risk
group.
Mhm.
And if we're attributed to difference in
radiation,
we'd expect that placebo group to look
different in terms of that timing.
You know, these are, you know, yeah.
I think one thing worth worth saying is
just the you know the I think Suzanne's
comment about cancer specific mortality
is relevant for this discussion as well.
I think there were a number of guests in
the keto trial.
Related to COVID or something to that
effect.
So I think you know kind of world world
events may be irrelevant as well that
Correct.
could could shed some light on the
difference between the two treatment arms
in these in these studies.
Like if you ran both these studies again,
would we see the same results if we did
Color.
random now like?
I guess it's probably not,
but that's just my bias.
And anyone want to speculate that the
frequency of dosing which started more
frequently some alipumab and then
expanded versus the pembro which was Q6
weeks from the get go.
Might have enough difference in minimal
microscopic residual disease.
And.
Oh.
I I don't.
I don't have any reason to believe that,
but there's a difference.
There is a difference.
That one. You know, one thing we haven't.
I would,
I would believe that well before I would
believe that there's a difference between
the two anti PD ones in squamous cell
Right. Uh.
cancer.
We don't have that much data about Q6
dosing in.
Squame.
And of course it means that the 2nd dose
is given a long,
long time after the patient had surgery
or radiation, whatever. But like I said.
If you try to go the other way,
reverse engineer it,
it would be hard to figure out how how
you could make these changes and expect a
50 point loss of hazard ratio, right? And.
You know,
you'd expect big differences in the
placebo group.
It is.
David,
do you know what percentage of the
keynote trial patients were from outside
the US?
No, my head.
Because that, you know,
I was surprised at the proportion in the
Semiplimab trial and there may be some
subtle differences in practice.
Yeah.
Yeah, I have that open here.
It looks like maybe 108 patients in the
US and then maybe 100 and sixty 260 / 300
patients. Yeah.
So it was primarily an ex U.S. study,
but they they, yeah,
it's unclear how many they had nostril.
But yeah, of there are 400 or so patients,
only 100 were in the US. I'm just,
S.
I'm looking at the slides here, yeah.
See.
Mm-hmm. Thanks.
OK.
Yeah.
So Vernon,
I I think that this slide right here,
Hi.
Yeah.
I would have thought this hypothesis was
ridiculous with you.
Like is there any difference?
But I'm curious like Regeneron on the
phone like you feel strongly that dose
and drug matters that you're doing a
head-to-head Nivo rele versus.
Semifanlumab in Melanoma. Nikhil,
you have a poster and right and ASCO
about it.
So you feel like there's enough to either
dose or drug that you're going to go
head-to-head with it with,
you know what I would have said it all,
they're all the same, you know,
Lag 3 and PD1 to I don't know what you
can say, you know enough.
Public call like this, but like what?
What are the thoughts about drug and dose?
Yeah, I mean.
Like clearly you think it matters?
I know I just want to be careful about
that because that study,
the head-to-head you're referring to is
you know the Regeneron lag 3 plus PD1
versus Updalog.
So it's the lag three-part where there's
Right.
a big dose difference and you know there
was therefore.
Question to does that matter and do a
head to head study.
So when we're talking about just one PD1
versus another,
you know there isn't that such an obvious
reason you know to kind of want to do a
study like that, right.
So but I would say in.
Another study that's going on,
you know we we we don't have head-to-head
data of Pembro against Semi in any
prospective study.
There is a small data set that may become
available later in the year or next year
in Melanoma.
I don't know that will really be that
illuminating.
Yeah.
So I I it would be very nice to see the
kind of grant.
I think Doctor Sondak made the point
before that we don't have the granularity
on the hazard ratios.
I also like Doctor Kaplan's discussion of
looking at CSC specific death and much
the way people look at Melanoma specific
death.
There were a lot of deaths on the on the
on the Keynote 630 trial.
Please double check to make sure you're
people to talk about this time.
If you're up and bound to habit,
please go back to your seat and secure
your falcon with your seat belt.
Thank you.
So someone's going getting an early start
on the weekend,
and I hope it's someplace fun that you're
going to. But yeah,
there's just so much missing data that it
makes it difficult to do a hard
comparison of Keynote 630 versus C Post,
but.
Yeah, so I, you know,
trying to answer the question,
but I I don't want to overstep and go
beyond where the data are.
No, I totally agree.
And and I guess I'm also like responding
to Isaac's question about dose mattering,
which I think is was interesting because
I I guess you know, yes,
the PD1 you're saying cemiplimab in nivo,
not not sure that you really think
there's a difference there,
but it's the lag 3,
but it's still this idea that an antibody.
Could be more efficacious either just
based on its biological activity or dose.
And I think that that logic that I
haven't thought a lot about.
And then I saw that study and I was like,
OK,
Regeneron clearly believes a dose in
antibody matters to run a head-to-head.
And then this study, like,
who knows what the actual biology is,
but it isn't something I've thought a lot
about other than I've always assumed it,
you know, an antibody.
So once, yeah.
But David, you know,
I think it's it's a fascinating question
again that you ask.
And if you go back in time and look at
the original Empower data for cemiplimab
approval and you look at the Keynote 629
data that led to and the other study
Karskin that led to Pembro approval.
Admittedly,
they were slightly different patient
populations and the definitions of
locally advanced versus metastatic were
different between the two groups at first
initial value. If you look at Grobe study,
which is keynote,
the response rate was about 38% to to
pembrolizumab, whereas.
Semiplimab,
it was consistently between 45 to 51,
depending on which Empower subgroup you
looked at.
When you looked at PFS on both of those,
the median PFS on the Semiplimab study
was about 18 months for locally advanced
and metastatic patient.
It was 8 1/2 months for pembrolizumab.
Now when you parse out and further sort
of dive into the data in terms of number
of prior lines of therapy and how that
impacted response rate,
then you could sort of make the argument
that these drugs are inherently similar.
I think most of us.
Inherently believe they're similar,
but I think this clearly asks that
question. You know,
could there actually be a difference in
CSCC? I don't know the answer,
but I always would struggle with the
Empower versus Keynote metastatic locally
advanced data and try to say, OK,
if you're going to design a follow-up
study to that, what should?
Compared to RMB,
it would be easier to beat pembrolizumab
if you believe that it's an inferior drug,
but I don't know the answer.
But I think there's also the question of
therapeutic intent versus adjuvant in in
I agree.
a minimal residual disease setting, right.
But that could also have differences that
we're unaware of based on the therapeutic
intent, locally advanced metastatic.
Greed.
Other comments, thoughts.
You know, the one topic, David,
perhaps we didn't dive into yet in this
discussion is this is maybe it's too much
to tackle at 4:27,
but what is the role of radiation here
and is there an appetite?
M.
Unlabel or not for skipping the radiation
piece and for those who want to give anti
PD1 in the adjuvant setting,
you know who who's interested in thinking
about just moving straight to
cementplumab and avoiding radiation?
I'll I'll say how about irrespective of
length of treatment,
there are probably some some folks that
might say I'm interested but I don't want
to give it for a year like I could
envision that but.
As folks interpret this when they said
yes, I'm, I'm comfortable.
I'm in that comfortable group.
What's happening in the real world in the
next six months?
Yeah, I think it's interesting. You know,
when when Vern said you,
you talk about tumor board a year ago,
you're talking about the radiation
oncology colleagues.
You're making an argument that like,
you know,
you're gonna subject systemic therapy at
10 to 15% risk of a serious adverse event.
You have a standard of care approach
includes radiation.
And you know,
I think we the study was done because we
need to improve that standard of care
approach.
But I guess I've seen a lot of people
suffer from radiation, right?
The toxicity,
the long lasting sequelae of radiation
that.
You know,
if this patient came in and said,
you know, I'd like to avoid radiation.
I was, I would go,
I think there are many situations where I
would say, you know,
I would express the caveat that this
study was done. We don't have data.
This is really a data free zone to treat
you without it.
But I would be comfortable with that
patient preference if we had an informed
conversation because of the toxicity.
Radiation, I mean, hearing loss, like I,
you know, permanent hearing loss,
that's a big deal.
I've seen that in several patients. Yeah,
I'm sure others people have as well.
You know,
taste disturbances for the rest of their
life.
Osteoradial necrosis,
I mean stuff that's really toxic.
So that that's,
I mean that's just that's that's my
perspective in the next six months I
could see or I guess probably more than
six months.
I don't know where this is in its
pipeline for like a PDUFA date or or I'm
sure that stuff is already I don't.
Whether it's publicly available or not,
but I imagine there's PDUFA date in
January or something in 2026,
but or something along that line.
But I I imagine this conversation is
gonna happen more and more once it gets
approved.
But I think those conversations can
happen now because the data is out there.
We have this data,
so we don't necessarily need an approval.
We have the data.
But if you if you just do the thought
experiment,
how would the data look if you hadn't
radiated anybody on the trial?
Obviously the placebo arm would have more
recurrences.
We we think,
or else the whole idea of radiation is a
bad idea,
and presumably so with the treated arm
have more recurrences,
at least local regional recurrences,
because they didn't have radiation among
that.
Population that wasn't benefiting from
the immunotherapy. On the flip side,
the salvage option now is to radiate them,
right?
Right.
So you are you are trading one thing for
another.
You you're saving something for later.
And and that's not a bad thing.
I think the so it's a very pertinent
question.
It's also a pertinent question in
neoadjuvant therapy.
Our approach at Moffitt has been.
That we're not comfortable.
Just give a couple,
3-4 doses of neoadjuvant therapy and if
it's a good response, declare victory,
walk away, do nothing else.
We've done one of two things.
We've tended to go with a consolidation
approach, say either surgery or radiation.
Let's do something so that we can,
especially if we're treating, you know,
we're treating disease that was.
Restricted to the scalp or restricted to
the nodal basin.
Radiate it if you don't want to operate,
but do something if you've had a very
good clinical response,
and then declare victory.
Or alternatively say I'm not going to do
anything else,
I'm going to treat this as I would
unresectable disease and I'm going to
continue to give systemic therapy until I
am sure that it's a it's a clinical
complete response.
And then I would treat beyond the first
scan showing CR and give that patient a
longer duration of systemic therapy.
So there are we still don't know which of
those approaches.
Better if there's any difference,
if there's even any value in in anything
besides the first few doses of
immunotherapy.
But these are really important questions
to try to tease out because our patients
care about those things.
Agreed. And and Speaking of questions,
the Regeneron team,
do you guys have questions for us?
Matthew, Frank, Chris, Allison,
any anyone have questions you guys have
been thinking as this conversation has
gone on?
I think about them and then someone
brings it up. So I've got some notes here.
I mean, it's just, you know,
it's just an absolute pleasure to hear
this kind of thoughtful dialogue about
something we worked a lot of years on and
you know,
we're in the process of trying to figure
out how we're going to.
Discuss this potential new treatment
option, you know,
depending obviously the FDA reviews and
stuff like that with a broader community.
So yeah, I don't know.
I'll leave my colleagues to jump in if I
if there was a topic that they wanted to
touch on, but I mean.
I see the conversation going directions.
Oh,
maybe I'll bring this up and then someone
would bring it up. So it's just great.
Perfect.
No, I I agree. I mean,
it's been great to really hear
everybody's comments.
Including some of the big questions that
remain to be tackled, such as, you know,
what's the relative benefit of
neoadjuvant versus adjuvant versus
perioperative and what is actually the
biology of immunotherapy in either
settings.
So there's a lot of questions that we
still.
That we still have, but you know,
everything we do is also incremental.
I mean this as as you know,
I think as Vishal mentioned earlier,
this has been a study.
It took us a long time to to do this
study. It's not,
it's not an easy thing to do and it's
also incremental work.
It's not to to to minimize any of those
important questions,
but it it it takes it takes a lot of
effort to to to tackle each one of those.
Great.
All right, Team. Well, it's 435.
If there are no additional questions,
that was an awesome discussion.
Thank you everybody for joining. We'll,
we'll pick a time for August or September
for our next journal club.
We have a couple good suggestions already.
And I'll adjourn. Thanks everybody.
Thank you again.
That was a great discussion.
Thanks for having us. Thank you.
Thank you everyone. Bye. Thanks.
Thanks. Bye.
Thank you.
I team.
Take care.
I mean.
Right.
It's a lot of drug, you know.
Yeah.
It's a great question. You know,
I feel like these sessions like this,
I mean, there's a lot of emotions,
a lot of thoughts.
One that like comes to the top is like,
I need a break. Like I'm not like,
you know, like not like that,
like a long period, but like,
am I ready to gear?
You're up for August again. It's like,
I don't know,
maybe every other month might be a better
fit for me just because it like takes up
a ton. I mean,
I get into stuff like that reconstructed
individual patient data stuff took way
longer than I thought it was going to.
As these things often do,
but it was sort of like, hey,
I've never really done this before.
I I I kind of did it with BMS on a on a
manuscript that we have out,
but they did most of the legwork with it.
So this is the first time I did it and I
realized like stuff that I actually used
for that paper.
Isn't that great?
Like the there are algorithms that you
can use to to extract individual patient
data, but like until you do it,
you don't know how good they are.
And my experience was poor,
like doesn't reconstitute it very well,
so you have to do a lot of legwork
yourself.
But it does allow you to do stuff like
that. That's interesting.
It generates ideas.
You know there are matched adjust
indirect comparison studies that can be
done with this data. So once you have it,
there are some things we can play with,
which is.
Interesting.
I do think it makes the perspective
pieces more interesting when we have
extra stuff. It's not just commentary,
like the alluvial plot that was.
That's actually kind of cool.
That's a cool little visualization.
ALLUVIAL. Alluvial.
Wasn't it cool looking? I mean,
it takes a while to process.
You gotta like, what's going on here?
But 'cause I always do wonder sometimes
I'm like, I wonder who's doing this.
You know, it's really,
I'm only looking at question by question
like who's using adjuvant immunotherapy?
And now you can see, oh,
it's a dermatologist or, you know, oh,
it's a Mohs surgeon that said they're
recommending it. So that's kind of fun,
you know, but it's more of a.
It's in a paper.
You can spend some time looking at it as
opposed to a presentation where it's
overwhelming and you just can't process
what you're looking at.
So those things were interesting,
like they're fun and new. But yeah,
I mean the conversation.
I think because of the people that show
up, like we are who we are.
So like my approach to all of the
clinical situations over the last couple
years with this group is kind of the same.
So like you kind of expect the same stuff
like Vern and Nikhil, like that Moffit,
they practice away.
That tends to be a little more
conservative.
I also think people like Suzanne and
stuff like they present these things as
like, oh, I heard this, you know,
from you guys, not very scientific,
blah blah blah, you know,
the assumptions we're making.
But it's like, what are you doing, right?
Yes.
Right. So I mean, are people.
I think people are worried that they're
going to be judged,
which we are when we make these comments.
But like, if I don't volunteer, like,
this is what I'm going to do,
then the conversation doesn't get
interesting. It doesn't get deep like.
People just like, well, you know,
the data doesn't say this,
so therefore I'm not, you know, like,
I'm not gonna act. You're like, well,
what are you gonna do then?
It's only I I only I just don't know her
that well and I think she's you know like
there are comments that she made to be it
when she came to the the checkmark 358.
It's more of like it is in that vein that
like.
Not being that scientific and it's sort
of like, well,
we practice in the Gray zone, man,
like that's where we live.
And I'll tell you what I'm going to do
because I got to make these decisions.
So I mean, I'll air it out. You know,
I think people tend to be a little
conservative on these calls.
Or my my, I mean,
I might just be interpreting it wrong,
but I feel like people will say like
things in the abstract,
but they don't say like they don't put
their nickel down like I'm gonna practice
this way. It's more like indirect. Oh,
it's interesting.
We don't have data on that.
You know, it is these glancing comments,
but not really getting to the heat of it,
the meat of it.
Yeah.
But I actually don't know what Bern is
going to do tomorrow.
So like, he does speak his mind,
but like I actually, but again,
it was a little like shifty and not
specific. I mean,
he said he's ambivalent on the radiation.
So I I mean it's, but I was like,
I am comfortable if this person says they
don't want radiation.
No one else said yes to that, right?
No one else said. I mean, you nodded.
You were like, yeah, I mean,
obviously you and I practice.
So I didn't need that response from you,
but like, was anybody else?
Yeah.
He did. Yeah, yeah.
I think people need other people to say
this is what I'm gonna do.
So they'll be like, OK,
I'll do it too when they are practicing
alone.
Like Vishal doesn't really have a buddy.
And how much?
I don't know if he's making these
decisions or Julie's making these
decisions now. I don't know. You know,
Vache, like, I, you know, I don't know.
I mean,
I think as we have said time and time
again, like our group is special.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I don't know.
I but I I I mean it's great like Paul was
there against Suzanne.
Like these are these are people with get
a lot of stuff on their plate.
So they're coming cause they think it's a
worthwhile conversation and exercise that
always makes me happy.
But this was as good a group as the BMS.
Like,
I don't know how many people are on there.
I'm trying to pull the attendance,
but it was multiple. I mean,
that's the thing with teams.
I gotta figure out the window stuff.
But like I had to go through 3 pages and
I I don't love that, you know,
'cause I don't.
OK.
I mean, that's great.